



09667642440



gwenpena21@gmail.com



Mabalacat City, Pampanga

Links

LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/linkedin-gwynethpena

Github: https://bit.ly/github-gwyneth-pena

PeoplePerHour: https://bit.ly/pph-gwyneth-pena

Skills

- Angular
- Python
- Ionic
- CSS
- HTML
- Javascript
- Git
- Java
- React

Language

English

Filipino

Gwyneth Christine M. Peña

Software Engineer

A software engineer with 2+ years of experience working on web and mobile applications using various tech stacks such as Angular, Python, and Ionic. Also, has previous experience as a freelancer creating WordPress sites and providing other web-related solutions for clients.

Experience

July 2022 - Present

Titanium Technologies, Inc.

Software Engineer

- Worked on web and mobile applications related to HRIS (Human Resource Information System) using Angular, Python, and Ionic.
- Helped the team to improve existing products by adding new features.
- Supported the team in testing and providing solutions to ensure responsiveness and efficiency of applications.

September 2020 - April 2022

PeoplePerHour

Self-Employed (Freelance Web Developer)

- Created WordPress sites for my clients.
- Helped clients to convert their Figma Designs to responsive web pages using HTML/CSS/JavaScript/Bootstrap.
- Worked on fixing website-related issues and provided solutions or other functionalities required by clients.

† February 2022 - April 2022

Toro Cloud

Frontend Intern

• Learned how to use AngularJS for creating CRUD applications.

Education

2018 - 2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

Holy Angel University

Reference

Jay Mark Ong

Team Leader, Titanium Trachnologies, Inc.

Phone: 09171239069 **Email:** <u>jay.ong@myoffice.ph</u>

Engr. Gina S. Tumang

Professor, Holy Angel University

 Phone:
 09171502746

 Email:
 gtumang@hau.edu.ph